i3investor.com 2014-11-22

# Privacy Policy | I3investor

Welcome to I3investor. Our Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, disclose, and protect information that applies to our Service, and your choices about the collection and use of your information.

I3investor may modify or update this Privacy Policy from time to time to reflect the changes in our business and practices, and so you should review this page periodically. When we change the policy in a material manner we will update the ‘last modified’ date at the bottom of this policy.

#### 1\. What information do we collect and how is it used?

Capitalized terms that are not defined in this Privacy Policy have the meaning given them in our Terms of Use. We collect the following types of information about you: 

**Information we receive from third parties:** I3investor is currently available to users who register with the I3investor portal directly, or users who login through Facebook account and authorize access through Facebook Connect. By connecting to I3investor with Facebook Connect, you give us permission to access, store and use your information from Facebook including, but not limited to, your Facebook UID, any information that you have permitted Facebook to share with us, any information you have made public in connection with that service, any interests that are not hidden and mutual friends that you may have in common with another User. You should always review, and if necessary, adjust your privacy settings on third-party websites and services before linking or connecting them to the Service. 

**Information you provide us directly:** We ask for certain information such as your first and last name, Facebook UID and e-mail address if you correspond with us or submit an inquiry. We may also retain any messages you send through the Service, and may collect information you provide in User Content you post to the Service. We use this information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the Service and to keep the site safe. 

**Analytics information.** We may directly collect analytics data, or use third-party analytics tools, to help us measure traffic and usage trends for the Service. These tools collect information sent by your browser that assist us in improving the Service. We collect and use this analytics information in aggregate form such that it cannot reasonably be manipulated to identify any particular individual user. 

**Cookies information:** When you visit the Service, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser and lets I3investor help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the site. A cookie may also convey information to us about how you use the Service, and allow us to track your usage of the Service over time. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the Service may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled. 

**Log file information:** Log file information is automatically reported by your browser each time you access the Service. When you use our Service, our servers automatically record certain log file information. These server logs may include anonymous information such as your web request, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, referring / exit pages and URLs, number of clicks and how you interact with links on the Service, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, and other such information. 

**Geo-location data:** When you access the Service, we may access, collect, monitor and/or remotely store “geo-location data,” which may include GPS coordinates (e.g. latitude and/or longitude) or similar information regarding your location. 

**Communications:** We use the information we collect or receive to communicate directly with you. We also use your information to send you Service-related emails (e.g., account verification, confirmations and reminders, changes/updates to features of the Service, product features, technical and security notices). 

**Use of certain service type information we collect about you:** We use or may use cookies, log file, device identifiers, location data and clear gifs information to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the site; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) to provide and monitor the effectiveness of our Service; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, traffic, and demographic patterns; (e) diagnose or fix technology problems; (f) help you efficiently access your information after you sign in; (g) to provide advertising and (h) to keep the site safe. 

#### 2\. Who is your information shared with?

We will not rent or sell your information to third parties outside I3investor (including any parent, subsidiaries and affiliates) without your consent, except as noted below:

**Who we may share your information with:** We may share your information with third-party business partners to assist them in providing a better experience for you and with partners that we have engaged to help ensure site safety. 

**What happens in the event of a change of control:** We may sell, assign or otherwise transfer user information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, acquisitions, bankruptcies, dissolutions, reorganizations, liquidations, similar transactions or proceedings involving all or a portion of the I3investor. 

**Instances where we are required to share your information:** I3investor will disclose your information where required to do so by law or subpoena or if we reasonably believe that such action is necessary to (a) comply with the law and the reasonable requests of law enforcement; (b) to enforce our Terms of Use or to protect the security or integrity of our Service; and/or (c) to exercise or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of I3investor, our Users or others. 

**Sharing certain service type information we collect about you:** We may share certain service type information, including information obtained through tools such as cookies, log files, device identifiers, location data and clear gifs (such as anonymous usage data, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.): (i) with our third-party business partners for the purposes described in the section above on “WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT AND HOW IS IT USED.” We may also aggregate or otherwise strip data of all personally identifying characteristics and may share that aggregated, anonymized data with third parties. 

**Ads on I3investor:** We may also share certain information such as your location, browser and cookie data and other data relating to your use of our Service with our business partners to deliver advertisements (“ads”) that may be of interest to you. I3investor may allow third-party ad servers or ad networks to serve advertisements on the Service. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser or mobile device, the ads and ad links that appear on the Service, and will automatically receive your IP address when they do so. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, device identifiers, location data, and clear gifs, see above) to compile information about your browser’s or device’s visits and usage patterns on the Service, and to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize the advertising content. I3investor does not sell, rent, or share the information we collect directly from you or about you from third parties with these third-party ad servers or ad networks for such parties’ own marketing purposes. 

Please note that an advertiser may ask I3investor to show an ad to a certain audience of Users (e.g., based on demographics or other interests). In that situation, I3investor determines the target audience and I3investor serves the advertising to that audience and only provides anonymous aggregated data to the advertiser. If you respond to such an ad, the advertiser or ad server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach.

The I3investor Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, third-party advertisers. Please consult the respective privacy policies of such advertisers or contact such advertisers for more information.

#### 3\. How is my information stored?

**Storage:** I3investor provides a place for social interaction via forum and comments and it provides you with the opportunity to create, submit, post, display, transmit, perform, publish, distribute or broadcast (“Post”) User Content. Any User Content you Post is subject to the guidelines provided in our Terms of Use and you should note that we reserve the right to report any potentially illegal behavior on our Service to the authorities. By using our Service, you are consenting to have your image and conversations recorded by I3investor. I3investor may take snapshots of User Content and may review User Content to maintain site safety and ensure a good user experience. 

**How long we keep your User Content:** You should be aware that text posts and comments may be saved indefinitely and snaps and User history on active accounts may also saved indefinitely. Should you choose to delete your I3investor account please email support@i3investor.com and we will make every effort to delete all snaps and User history within thirty (30) days of when the account is deleted. 

#### 4\. What steps do you take to keep my data safe?

**Keeping your information safe:** I3investor cares about the security of your information, and uses commercially reasonable safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of all information collected through the Service. However, I3investor cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to I3investor or guarantee that information on the Service may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed. Your privacy settings may also be affected by changes to the functionality of third party sites. I3investor is not responsible for the functionality or security measures of any third party. 

**Compromise of information:** In the event that any information under our control is compromised as a result of a breach of security, I3investor will take reasonable steps to investigate the situation and where appropriate, notify those individuals whose information may have been compromised and take other steps, in accordance with any applicable laws and regulations. 

#### 5\. How can I control my information?

**You control your account information and settings:** You may update your account information at any time by logging in to your account and changing your profile settings. If you have any questions about reviewing or modifying your account information, you can contact us directly at support@i3investor.com. 

**Opting out of collection of your information for Tracking / Advertising:** Please refer to your browser’s technical information for instructions on how to delete and disable cookies, and other tracking/recording tools. Note that disabling cookies and/or other tracking tools prevents I3investor or its business partners from tracking your browser’s activities in relation to the Service, and for use in targeted advertising activities by third parties. However, doing so may disable many of the features available through the Service. 

#### 6\. What about my privacy on other sites that I get to from I3investor?

We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites or services linked to or from the Service, including the information or content contained therein. Please remember that when you use a link to go from the Service to another website, our Privacy Policy and Terms of Use does not apply to third-party websites or services. In addition, you agree that we are not responsible and we do not control over any third-parties that you authorize to access your User Content. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information we collect by other means (including offline) or from other sources other than through the Service. 

#### 7\. Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.

#### 8\. How do I contact I3investor?

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the Terms of Use or the Service, please contact us at [support@i3investor.com](mailto:support@i3investor.com). 

This privacy policy was last modified on Nov 22, 2013.
